Tran Ngoc Minh Le

ngocminhletran2@gmail.com | Ho Chi Minh City https://www.linkedin.com/in/minh-le-1004/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A highly organized and hard-working individual looking forward for an entry-level within a constructive environment to gain valuable experience in Logistics and SCM industry. What I believe the most important when getting a job at the entry level is not a pay rate, but the invaluable experience I can earn from that job.

WORK HISTORY

EPC Health. North Melbourne Administrative Assistant | 06/2020 - 01/2023

- Assists doctors and physios with multiple roles in surgery administration support with hundreds of patients.
- Managing over 20 patients per day by taking messages and incoming calls.
- Handled client correspondence and tracked records to foster office efficiency.

Miquo Bubble Tea

General assistant | 11/2020 - 01/2023

- Establish a nice and warm working culture at the same time providing great customer service to increase sales.
- Restocked supplies and placed purchase orders with more than 100 SKUs to maintain adequate stock levels.
- Trained and mentored more than 10 new personnel hired to fulfill various roles.

AMA English Center. Ho Chi Minh Teaching assistant | 11/2018 - 05/2019

- Assisted teachers with classroom management and document coordination to maintain positive learning environment.
- Tutored more than 200 students individually and in small groups to reinforce learning concepts.

SKILLS

- Technician: Microsoft
 Word/ Excel/ PowerPoint,
 POS Systems, Blue chips
 System.
- Supplier Quotes
- Customer Inquiries
- Administrative Duties
- Beverage Service
- Resource Allocation
- Customer Satisfaction
- Workplace Restocking
- General Housekeeping
- · Advising and Coaching

EDUCATION

RMIT University

Melbourne, Australia, Australia 12/2022

Bachelor of Logistics And Supply Chain Management: Chain Management

GPA: 2.94/4.0

Gia Dinh High School

Ho Chi Minh 07/2018

High School Diploma

• Year 12's GPA: 9.2/10

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese: Native language

English: B2

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Procurement Management and Global Sourcing

The Old Coffee Saigon (University Assignment)

Responsibilities:

- Analyze procurement process of small enterprise based in Melbourne.
- Align theories and apply appropriate methods in the integration of procurement management.

Achievements:

- Build strong relationship with at least 3 employers in firm
- Explore valuable source of information in importing/ exporting and distributing coffee process in Australia.
- Procurement-Assessment-Task-2.pdf.download